# **LOGAN COLLINS**

# Senior Front-End Developer

**+1-516-654-4426** 

@ hermes8527@gmail.com

#### **EXPERIENCE**

## Senior Full Stack Blockchain Developer

#### **Brewlabs**

**=** 04/2023 - 03/2024

Phttps://brewlabs.info/

- Created the company landing page using React from the Figma design, featuring simple yet elegant components and smooth animations
- Created UI kit and unit test script to expedite front-end development for landing pages and on-chain services such as staking
- Implemented UI of Staking and Zap-In page and collaborated with Smart Contract engineers to integrate Web3
- Collaborated with company executives to improve performance and service utilities and expand community

### Senior Full Stack Blockchain Developer

#### SparkWorld\*

**=** 04/2022 - 03/2023

- Worked in the front-end development team of 5 members to build the company landing page in React
- Led a team of four front-end developers to develop the front-end of NFT Marketplace and Aggregator using the test-driven development approach
- Collaborated with Smart Contract engineers to integrate Web3 to buy NFTs through NFT Marketplace and Aggregator
- Used RESTful APIs provided by back-end developers with Swagger to get sale data and update transaction history

## Senior Full Stack Blockchain Developer

#### **Satang Technologies**

**=** 04/2020 - 03/2022

- Collaborated with a designer to create a modern, yet simple user interface for our company's landing page
- Developed individual components and composed them to implement pixel-perfect frontend from Figma design
- Took part in Asset Tokenizer project as a front-end developer and collaborated with Smart Contract engineer to utilize real-estate transaction on blockchain

## Senior Full Stack Developer

#### **Polisport**

**m** 04/2019 - 03/2020

Phttps://polisport.com/, https://polisportvirtualtour.com/

- Joined the company as a Full Stack Web Developer
- Collaborated with backend developers to retrieve products and services data for implementation of a pixel-perfect frontend in React from Figma
- Wrote unit test scripts for the front-end using Mocha and Jest libraries
- Led Polisport Virtual Tour Project and implemented main UI in React and virtual tour in 3d environment using Three.js library

## Full Stack Developer

### **Canary Technologies**

**=** 04/2016 - 03/2019

https://glassbororentals.com/, https://ventano.de/

- During my six-month internship as a developer, I gained valuable insights into the company's culture and development methodologies
- In the Glassboro Rentals project, I created smooth and visually appealing user interfaces as a front-end developer
- Designed MySQL database and contributed to three pages using Laravel framework as a Full Stack Developer in the Ventano project

#### **SUMMARY**

A seasoned front-end developer with 8+ years of experience in the web development industry. What sets me apart is the ability to learn new technologies, passion for the product and keen eye for detail.

I always create detailed workflows, progress stepby-step, and conduct thorough testing to ensure accuracy and timely development.

I enjoy proposing new ideas, wearing different hats, and collaborating with others to achieve success.

#### **EDUCATION**

## **Bachelor of Computer** Science

GPA

**DePaul Unversity** 

3.9 / 4.0

#### **SKILLS**

Frameworks & Libraries

		ux Next.js		Vue	Lit
		aterial UI	Boo	Bootstrap	
Tailwi	nd CSS	Web3			
Langua	ıges				
JavaScript		TypeScrip	t I	PHP	
Develo	pment 8	Operation	ns		
Scrum	n Agi	le			
Version	n Contro	ol Systems			
Git	GitHub	GitLak	) B	itbucke	t
Cloud S	Services				
AWS	GCP	Micros	Microsoft Azure		

#### STRENGTHS

Time Management
Communication
Teamwork